Leslie Crow Papers
Holt-Atherton Department of Special Collections
- Series III: Research Files, 1850-2006
  - Box 10
    - Subseries: Sacramento, 1891-2006
      - 10.10 Boulevard Park-Wright and Kimbrough Advertisements
      - 10.11 Camellia Cottage / Boiler Plant and Laundry
      - 10.12 Chemical Station Number Four
      - 10.13 City of Sacramento-Central City Preservation Update, 1996
      - 10.14 City of Sacramento-Historic Districts, 2005
      - 10.15 City of Sacramento-Historic Preservation Ordinance, 2001
      - 10.16 City of Sacramento-Historic Resources Inventory, 2000
      - 10.17 City of Sacramento-Incentives for Historic Preservation, 2000
      - 10.18 City of Sacramento-Listing of Historic Structures, 1998
      - 10.19 City of Sacramento-Preservation Element, 2000
      - 10.20 City of Sacramento-Report of Select Committee, 1997
      - 10.21 City of Sacramento-Request for Proposals, 2002
      - 10.22 Coloma School
      - 10.23 Colonial Theater
      - 10.24 Colonial Theater-Photographs, 2004
      - 10.25 Consulting Contract, 2002-2005
      - 10.26 Consulting Contract Proposals
      - 10.27 Ebners Hotel
      - 10.28 Federal Courthouse
      - 10.29 Firehouse Number Four
      - 10.30 Firehouse Number Four-Historical Finding
      - 10.31 Guide to Historic Homes
      - 10.32 Heilbron Mansion
      - 10.33 Heilbron Mansion-Historical Finding
      - 10.34 Oak Park (1 of 2)
      - 10.35 Oak Park (2 of 2)
      - 10.36 Old Sacramento Historical Inventory, 1962
      - 10.37 Research Institutions in Sacramento
      - 10.38 Restoration Resources
      - 10.39 Sacramento Archives
      - 10.40 Sacramento Guides
      - 10.41 Sutter, John
      - 10.42 Thomas Jefferson Elementary School
      - 10.43 Tower Bridge
      - 10.44 Trinity Cathedral
      - 10.45 Trinity Cathedral Photographs, 2004
  - Box 11
    - Subseries: Sacramento, 1891-2006 (cont.)
      - 11.1 Union Race Track
      - 11.2 Weinstock Lubin Catalog, 1891
      - 11.3 Westminster Presbyterian
      - 11.4 Westminster Presbyterian-Photographs, 2003
      - 11.5 Various Residences-915 Eleventh Street
      - 11.6 Various Residences-2025 P Street
      - 11.7 Various Residences-2025 P Street, Photographs
      - 11.8 Various Residences-324 U Street
      - 11.9 Various Notes, Articles, and Photographs
    - Subseries: San Francisco County and City, 1906-1936
      Includes book, newspaper articles, and photographs.
      - 11.10 San Francisco1906 Earthquake
    - Subseries: San Joaquin County, 1851-2005
      Includes newspaper articles, correspondence, research notes, reports, agreements, meeting minutes, consulting proposals, brochures, invoices, photographs, commission agendas, maps, historical articles, photocopied books and chapters, list of historic landmarks, project description, paperwork in support of national registration, meeting minutes, pamphlets, and petitions and supporting documents for historic designation.
      - 11.11 Agriculture-San Joaquin County
      - 11.12 Clements I.O.O.F. Hall
      - 11.13 Cosumnes River
      - 11.14 Escalon
      - 11.15 French Camp
      - 11.16 Grain Article
      - 11.17 Grapes / Vineyards / Wine
      - 11.18 Italians in San Joaquin County
      - 11.19 Lathrop
      - (See Oversize, Box 24) Linden Irrigation District
      - 11.20 Lathrop Italian POW Recognition Project
      - 11.21 Lodi, California
      - 11.22 Lodi Jail
      - 11.23 Mokelumne City
      - 11.24 San Joaquin County-1886, Ellis, W. R.
      - 11.25 San Joaquin County-General
      - 11.26 San Joaquin County Rail Commission
      - 11.27 Sedgwick, Thomas (Lathrop)
      - 11.28 SJRTD-Lindsay Street, 2004
      - 11.29 South San Joaquin Irrigation District
      - 11.30 South San Joaquin Irrigation District Line-CEQA Project
      - 11.31 Summer Home
      - 11.32 Tracy
      - 11.33 Women Pioneers in S.J. County
      - 11.34 Woodbridge, California
      - 11.35 Woodbridge Masonic Lodge (1 of 2)
      - 11.36 Woodbridge Masonic Lodge (2 of 2)
      - (See Oversize, Box 25) Woodbridge Masonic Lodge History
    - Subseries: Solano County, 1973-2004
      Includes correspondence, newspaper photocopies and clippings, photographs, handwritten notes, applications and paperwork in support of designation for city landmark status and national registration, consulting proposals, historic conservation plans, maps, unpublished histories, brochures, newsletters, note cards, diagrams, planning commission agendas, architectural drawings, historic preservation ordinances, inventories, and volunteer guidelines.
      - 11.37 Benicia
      - 11.38 Benicia-Consulting
      - 11.39 Benicia-Historic Preservation
      - 11.40 Dixon and Elmira
      - 11.41 Rio Vista
      - 11.42 Vacaville-528 Main Street
      - 11.43 Vacaville-City Planning
      - 11.44 Vacaville-Graphics
      - 11.45 Vacaville-Historic Preservation
      - 11.46 Vacaville-Historic Resources Inventories
      - 11.47 Vacaville-Publicity (1 of 2)
      - 11.48 Vacaville-Publicity (2 of 2)
      - 11.49 Vallejo
  - Box 12
    - Subseries: Stockton, 1850-2006
      Includes correspondence, newspaper photocopies and clippings, slides, photographs, digital images, handwritten notes, applications and paperwork in support of designation for city landmark status and national registration, studies of historic properties and structures, published and unpublished histories, school projects, and maps.
      - 12.1 Aaron, Henry, Residence
      - 12.2 Adams, Harriet Chalmers / Adams, Franklin Pierce
      - 12.3 Adelaide (brig) / Arcade Saloon
      - 12.4 African Americans
      - 12.5 Agricultural Hall
      - 12.6 All the Kings Men
      - 12.7 Allen, Glenn
      - 12.8 American Red Cross, San Joaquin Chapter-One Hundred Years
      - 12.9 Ancient Egyptian Order of Sciots
      - 12.10 Anthony, Susan B.
      - 12.11 Anti-Chinese Reports
      - 12.12 Arcade Clothing Store
      - 12.13 Archaeology
      - 12.14 Architecture
      - 12.15 Architects-Biographical Sketches
      - 12.16 Architects-King, Walter
      - 12.17 Architects-Rushforth, George
      - 12.18 Architects-Warner, Franklyn E
      - 12.19 Armory-California and Harding Way
      - (See Rolled Oversize Maps and Plans, Box 26) Armory Plans, 1916
      - 12.20 Armory-Weber Point
      - 12.21 Arndt Building
      - 12.22 Arndt, M. S.
      - 12.23 Atherton, Warren / G.I. Bill
      - 12.24 Austin Brothers
      - 12.25 Automobiles
      - 12.26 Aviation History
      - 12.27 Avon Theater
      - 12.28 Babe Bean
      - 12.29 Bank of Stockton Corporation
      - 12.30 Bank of Stockton Archives
      - 12.31 Banks, Albertis Leon
      - 12.32 Banner Island
      - 12.33 Baptists
      - 12.34 Baseball-Stockton Nine
      - 12.35 Beasley, Charles
      - 12.36 Beaver
      - 12.37 Beck Development
      - 12.38 Belding Building
      - 12.39 Belding Building-Proposal
      - 12.40 Belding, Charles
      - 12.41 Belli, Melvin
      - 12.42 Belt, George G.
      - 12.43 Bennet Apartments
      - 12.44 Berachah Home
      - 12.45 Bernhardt, Sarah
      - 12.46 Besotes
      - 12.47 Big Tree Exhibit
      - 12.48 Biography
      - 12.49 Bishop Cut / Turner Cut Proposal
      - 12.50 Branch Building
      - 12.51 Bours Park Residences
      - 12.52 Bours Tract
      - 12.53 Boxing
      - 12.54 Brick Making-Local
      - 12.55 Bronx Hotel
      - 12.56 Brown, Edgar B.
      - 12.57 Budd, Inez Merrill
      - 12.58 Budd, John
      - 12.59 Buddhist Temple
      - 12.60 Buffalo Bill
      - 12.61 Builders Building
      - 12.62 Buildings
      - 12.63 Busses
      - 12.64 Caine, John
      - 12.65 California Building
      - 12.66 Canneries
      - 12.67 Cannery Strike, 1937-Bloody Friday
      - 12.68 Carson, James, H.-Early Recollections of the Mines
      - 12.69 Carson, William, and Mary Isabella Carson
      - 12.70 Castelli and Webers Saloon
      - 12.71 Catholic Cemetery
      - 12.72 Cat Stories
      - 12.73 Cemeteries
      - 12.74 Centennial Celebration, 1876
      - 12.75 Central Methodist Church
      - 12.76 Central Valley Project-Bradford S. Crittenden
      - 12.77 Chamber of Commerce
      - 12.78 Chang and Eng in Stockton
      - 12.79 Charles E. Pike Building
      - 12.80 Childrens Games
      - 12.81 Childrens Home of Stockton
      - 12.82 Chinese Heritage
      - 12.83 Christmas in Stockton
      - 12.84 Cineplex Project
      - 12.85 Circus
      - 12.86 City of Stockton, 1850-1860
      - 12.87 City of Stockton, 1874
      - 12.88 Civil War in Stockton
      - 12.89 Clark Building
      - 12.90 Clark and Henery
      - 12.91 Clowes Family
      - 12.92 Clowes Residence / Charlottes Oaks (1 of 2)
      - 12.93 Clowes Residence / Charlottes Oaks (2 of 2)
      - (See Rolled Oversize Maps and Plans, Box 26) Clowes Residence Alteration Plans, 1939
      - 12.94 Cohn Family
      - 12.95 Colberg Shipyards
      - 12.96 Collegeville
      - 12.97 Commercial and Savings Bank
      - 12.98 Congregational Church
      - 12.99 Confucius Church
      - 12.100 Connor, Patrick Edward
      - 12.101 Cool Corner
      - 12.102 Corral Hollow
      - 12.103 CSUS Stockton-Feasibility Study, 2000
      - (See VHS Cassettes, Box 23) Cunningham Hotel Issue, City Council, 1998
  - Box 13
    - Subseries: Stockton, 1850-2006 (cont.)
      - 13.1 Cunningham, Thomas, and Family
      - 13.2 Dagohoy Lodge, No. 528, L.D.T.
      - 13.3 Dalmatian Benevolent Society
      - 13.4 Darrah, Joan
      - 13.5 Davis-Hiller-Pearce Company
      - 13.6 Dawson Storage
      - 13.7 De Carli, Millio
      - 13.8 De Carli Plaza
      - 13.9 Delta Hotel
      - 13.10 Delta Story
      - 13.11 DeVinny, R. Harold
      - 13.12 Dickinson / Peck Wedding
      - 13.13 Dog Stories
      - 13.14 Downtown Hotels-Legal
      - (See VHS Cassettes, Box 23) Downtown Stockton: Past, Present, and Future, 2001
      - 13.15 Dr. Hunts Seminary
      - 13.16 Dunne, Edward
      - 13.17 Earle Hotel
      - 13.18 Earthquakes
      - 13.19 East Side Firehouse
      - 13.20 East Side Presbyterian Church
      - 13.21 Eberhardt, R. L.
      - 13.22 Eberhardt, R. M.
      - 13.23 Eden Square Apartments
      - 13.24 Eight Mile Road
      - 13.25 El Dorado Brewery
      - 13.26 El Dorado Bridge
      - 13.27 Elks Building
      - 13.28 Emergency Hospital
      - 13.29 Enterprise Planing Mill Fire
      - 13.30 Essential Services Building
      - 13.31 Explosion, 1879
      - 13.32 Farmers and Merchants Bank
      - 13.33 Ferries
      - 13.34 Filipino-Americans in Stockton
      - 13.35 First Christian Church
      - 13.36 First Church of Christ, Scientist
      - 13.37 First Presbyterian Church
      - 13.38 Fitzgerald, Michael
      - 13.39 Flaco, Juan
      - 13.40 Fog
      - 13.41 Fox California Theatre-Business Plan, 1996
      - (See Oversize, Box 24) Fox California Theatre-Publicity
      - 13.42 Fox California Theatre-Stockton (1 of 2)
      - 13.43 Fox California Theatre-Stockton (2 of 2)
      - (See VHS Cassettes, Box 23) Fox Theater in Stockton, 1996
      - 13.44 Fremont, John C.
      - 13.45 Friedberger Building
      - 13.46 Frogs
      - 13.47 Funk, J. E.
      - 13.48 Galgiani, Oscar
      - 13.49 Gardens
      - 13.50 Gerlach, Louis
      - 13.51 Gerlach, Wagner, and Company, Meat Market
      - 13.52 Gillis, James
      - 13.53 Gleason, Edna and Thomas
      - 13.54 Gleason Park
      - 13.55 Gnekow Building / Gnekow Hotel
      - 13.56 Gnekow, Rudolph
      - 13.57 Goddess of Justice
      - 13.58 Gold Rush-Stockton
      - 13.59 Goldsworthy Arson Case (1899)
      - (See VHS Cassettes, Box 23) The Good Old Days Remembered
      - 13.60 Gordon, Laura DeForce
      - 13.61 Grace Methodist Church
      - 13.62 Graham Brothers Trucks (1 of 2)
      - 13.63 Graham Brothers Trucks (2 of 2)
      - 13.64 Grand Central Hotel
      - 13.65 Gratton, Christopher, M.D.
      - 13.66 Greyhound Depot
      - 13.67 Gridley, Ruel Colt
      - 13.68 Griffits Block (Yale Apartments)
      - 13.69 Gummer Department Store
      - 13.70 Haas, Charles-Jeweler
      - 13.71 Haggin Museum
      - 13.72 Hahn, Adolph
      - 13.73 Hammer Ranch
      - 13.74 Hammond, John
      - 13.75 Hammond, Moses
      - 13.76 Hammond, R. P.
      - 13.77 Hansel and Ortman
      - 13.78 Hart and Thrift
      - 13.79 Hazelton Library
      - 13.80 Heald Building
      - 13.81 Henery Apartments
      - (See Rolled Oversize Maps and Plans, Box 26) Henery Apartments Plans
      - 13.82 Henery Apartments Proposal, 2003
      - 13.83 Hickinbotham Brothers-One Hundred Years
      - 13.84 Holden Drug Company
      - 13.85 Holt, Benjamin
      - 13.86 Holt Manufacturing Company
      - 13.87 Horan, W. J., Building
      - 13.88 Hotel Clark
      - 13.89 Hotel Cunningham
      - 13.90 Hotel Philson Fire
      - 13.91 Hotel St. Leo
      - 13.92 Hotel Stockton (1 of 2)
      - 13.93 Hotel Stockton (2 of 2)
      - (Rolled Oversize Maps and Plans, Box 26) Hotel Stockton, Rehabilitation Plans, 2002
      - 13.94 Hotels-Stockton
      - 13.95 Hotel Terry
      - 13.96 Hubbard, Maria S.
      - 13.97 Humbarger, Elizabeth
      - 13.98 Hunter Plaza
      - 13.99 Indexes
      - 13.100 Inglis, William
  - Box 14
    - Subseries: Stockton, 1850-2006 (cont.)
      - 14.1 Internment, World War II
      - 14.2 Internment, World War IIJapanese
      - 14.3 I.O.O.F. History
      - 14.4 I.O.O.F. Library Foundation, 1857-1867
      - 14.5 Italians in Stockton
      - 14.6 Jewish Cemetery (1 of 2)
      - 14.7 Jewish Cemetery (2 of 2)
      - 14.8 Jewish Community-Chronology and Notes
      - 14.9 Jewish Community-Research
      - 14.10 Jory, John
      - 14.11 Joss House
      - 14.12 Julia-Riverboat
      - 14.13 Kelsey, John Milton
      - 14.14 Kelsey, Nancy
      - 14.15 Kennedy, Glenn
      - 14.16 Keys, T. J., Residence
      - 14.17 King Albert and Queen Elizabeth of Belgium in Stockton
      - 14.18 King, Walter E.
      - 14.19 Klamath-Duraflame
      - 14.20 Knights of Columbus
      - 14.21 Ladbrooke Casino Project
      - 14.22 KVIE: Stockton: The Good Old Days
      - 14.23 Le Doux, Emma
      - 14.24 Lemurian Treasure
      - 14.25 Lester, Andrew
      - 14.26 Levy Brothers Building
      - 14.27 Lewis, Tillie Weisberg
      - 14.28 Lincoln, Abraham, Stockton Celebrations
      - 14.29 Lincoln Village
      - 14.30 Lindley, Albert
      - 14.31 Littlehale, James
      - 14.32 Little Manila
      - 14.33 Little Manila Historic District
      - 14.34 Little Manila Historic District, National Register Nomination
      - 14.35 Little Manila Site Survey
      - 14.36 Locke, Dean Jewett
      - 14.37 Locke Family Genealogy
      - 14.38 Lomax, Dr. L. M.
      - 14.39 London, Jack
      - 14.40 Losekann, Joseph
      - 14.41 Louttit, James Alexander
      - 14.42 Luther Locke Meat Market
      - 14.43 McGurk, Raymond T.
      - 14.44 McKee Building
      - 14.45 McKinley in Stockton, 1901
      - 14.46 McLeod Lake
      - 14.47 McMullin Building
      - 14.48 McNoble, George F., History
      - 14.49 Magnolia District
      - 14.50 Magnolia District / Midtown
      - 14.51 Magnolia District, Walk Tour Notes
      - 14.52 Magnolia House Hotel
      - 14.53 Mail Building
      - 14.54 Main Street
      - (See Oversize, Box 24) Maps of Stockton, 1850-1923
      - 14.55 Mariposa Hotel
      - 14.56 Marsh, John / Marsh Creek Road
      - 14.57 Masonic Lodge No. 19, Stockton
      - 14.58 Masonic Temple
      - 14.59 Masons in Stockton
      - 14.60 Mather, Stephen
      - 14.61 Matteson and Williamsons Plow Works
      - 14.62 Mayo, Frank V.
      - 14.63 Meader, C. T.
      - 14.64 Meader Family History
      - 14.65 Medico-Dental Building
      - 14.66 Methodist Church-Agricultural Hall
      - 14.67 Miller Dishwasher Company
      - 14.68 Miller, William P., Carriage Works
      - 14.69 Mineral Baths
      - 14.70 Miracle Mile-Pacific Avenue
      - 14.71 Monarch Foundry
      - 14.72 Morada Ranch
      - 14.73 Moreing, Arthur, Nellie, and Henry
      - 14.74 Motion Pictures
      - 14.75 Murietta, Joaquin
      - 14.76 Music / Musicians
      - 14.77 Naglee, Henry Morris
      - 14.78 Nast, Thomas-in Stockton
      - 14.79 Nation, Carrie
      - 14.80 Native Peoples
      - 14.81 Neumiller, Charles
      - 14.82 Newell, Sidney
      - 14.83 Newell, Sidney, Residence
      - 14.84 New Jerusalem
      - 14.85 Newspaper Art, 1850-1892
      - 14.86 Newspaper Editors
      - 14.87 Newspaper History
  - Box 15
    - Subseries: Stockton, 1850-2006 (cont.)
      - 15.1 Newspaper Notes, 1912-1913
      - 15.2 Newspaper Notes, 1915-1916
      - 15.3 Newspaper Notes, 1921
      - 15.4 Newspaper Notes, 1924
      - 15.5 Newspaper Notes, 1925
      - 15.6 Newspaper Notes, 1927
      - 15.7 Newspaper Notes, 1928-1930
      - 15.8 Newspaper Notes, 1931-1945
      - 15.9 Newspaper Notes, 1932-1933
      - 15.10 Nippon Hospital
      - 15.11 Northcrest
      - 15.12 Nutter, W. B.
      - 15.13 Oard, Paul
      - 15.14 Oard, Paul, Photos
      - 15.15 Oates, W. W.
      - 15.16 OConnor, W. B.
      - 15.17 Owen, Charles
      - 15.18 Oxford Manor
      - 15.19 Pacific Baths
      - 15.20 Pacific Gas and Electric Company
      - 15.21 Pacific Tannery
      - 15.22 Pacific Tannery Manuscript
      - 15.23 Paige and Webster
      - 15.24 Paper Mill
      - 15.25 Parker, R. B.
      - 15.26 Parkers Building
      - 15.27 Parks-Stockton
      - 15.28 Perino, Carmen
      - 15.29 Peters, J. D.
      - 15.30 Peyton, Valentine Mason
      - 15.31 Phillips, Lee A. / Reclamation
      - 15.32 Philomathean Club
      - 15.33 Philomathean Club Landmark Finding
      - 15.34 Philomathean Club Landmark Nomination
      - 15.35 Photograph Lists
      - 15.36 Photographer Lists
      - 15.37 Photographer Presentations
      - 15.38 Photographers
      - 15.39 Photographers-1850-1876
      - 15.40 Photographers-1876-1945
      - 15.41 Photographers-Batchelder, B. P.
      - 15.42 Photographers-Covello Collection
      - 15.43 Photographers-Covello, Leonard
      - 15.44 Photographers-Lea, Ralph
      - 15.45 Photographers-Martin, Van Covert
      - 15.46 Photographers-Stuart, W. M.
      - 15.47 Photographers-Wells / Rulofson
      - 15.48 Photographers-Wells, Thomas W.
      - 15.49 Photography-Stockton in Focus
      - 15.50 Place Names
      - 15.51 Port of Stockton
      - 15.52 Port of Stockton-in Western City, 1930
      - 15.53 Post Cards
      - 15.54 Post Office-Stockton
      - 15.55 Potato Day
      - 15.56 Prisoners of War in Stockton (World War II)
      - 15.57 Presbyterian Church
      - 15.58 Prostitution
      - 15.59 Purdy, Samuel
      - 15.60 Quinn Building
  - Box 16
    - Subseries: Stockton, 1850-2006 (cont.)
      - 16.1 Radio-Stockton
      - 16.2 Railroads
      - 16.3 Rainbow Rebekah Lodge-I.O.O.F.
      - 16.4 Red Men Hall-Shamrock
      - 16.5 Rendon, Cecil P.
      - 16.6 Renney Building
      - 16.7 Riis, Jacob
      - 16.8 Riverboats
      - 16.9 Rizal Social Club
      - 16.10 Roberts Island
      - 16.11 Rough and Ready Island
      - 16.12 Rough and Ready-Navy Transfer
      - 16.13 Rough and Ready, Quarters A
      - 16.14 Ruggles, Charles Lincoln
      - 16.15 Ruhl Building
      - 16.16 Ruhl, F. A.
      - 16.17 Rulofson, William Herman
      - 16.18 Rush of 49-1909
      - 16.19 Ruth, Babe
      - 16.20 Sala, Peter L.
      - 16.21 Salvation Army Building
      - 16.22 San Joaquin Building
      - 16.23 San Joaquin County Courthouse and Jail
      - 16.24 San Joaquin County Jail
      - 16.25 San Joaquin County Sheriffs Department
      - 16.26 San Joaquin Courthouse Image Debate
      - 16.27 San Joaquin Water Company Ditch
      - 16.28 Schools
      - 16.29 Schools-After Dark Publication
      - 16.30 Schools-Buildings
      - 16.31 Schools-Don Riggio School
      - 16.32 Schools-Educating Stockton
      - 16.33 Schools-El Dorado School
      - 16.34 Schools-Lafayette School
      - 16.35 Schools-Lincoln High School
      - 16.36 Schools-Luther Burbank School
      - 16.37 Schools-Profiles
      - 16.38 Schools-St. Gertrudes School
      - 16.39 Schools-St. Marys High School
      - 16.40 Schools-Stockton Female Institute
      - 16.41 Schools-Stockton High School
      - 16.42 Schools-SUSD History Book Project
      - 16.43 Schools-SUSD 150th Anniversary (1 of 2)
      - (See Oversize, Box 25) Schools-SUSD 150th Anniversary (2 of 2)
      - 16.44 Schools-Weber Primary School
      - 16.45 September 11 Anniversary, 2002
      - 16.46 Sewage Plan, 1888
      - 16.47 Shaw, H. C., Building
      - 16.48 Sherman, William T.
      - 16.49 Shima, George
      - 16.50 Shippee Home Ranch
      - 16.51 Shippee, L. U.
      - 16.52 Shippee, L. U., Residence, National Registration Nomination
  - Box 17
    - Subseries: Stockton, 1850-2006 (cont.)
      - 17.1 Shipyards
      - 17.2 Sikh Parade, 2004
      - 17.3 Sikhs in Stockton
      - 17.4 Sikh Temple
      - 17.5 Sikh Temple-City Landmark
      - 17.6 Sikh Temple-National Registration
      - 17.7 Sikh Temple-Photographs and Slides
      - 17.8 Simpson, Andrew, Residence
      - 17.9 Six, C. L.
      - 17.10 Skinner, J. Carroll, Kerosene Kate
      - 17.11 Smith, Frank Thornton
      - 17.12 Smith, George Falkenborough, House
      - 17.13 Social Life-Stockton, Nineteenth Century
      - 17.14 S.P. Depot
      - 17.15 Sperry Flour Company
      - 17.16 Sperry Office Building
      - 17.17 Spooner, John Pitcher
      - 17.18 Stagg, Amos Alonzo
      - 17.19 St. Agnes Academy
      - 17.20 St. Johns Episcopal
      - 17.21 St. Josephs Hospital
      - 17.22 St. Marys Catholic Church-Stockton
      - 17.23 St. Marys Parochial Residence
      - 17.24 Staples, Mary
      - 17.25 Starkweather Family
      - 17.26 Stephens Brothers Shipyard
      - 17.27 Stevensons Regiment
      - (See Oversize, Box 25) Stockton and Copperopolis Railroad Right of Way
      - 17.28 Stockton Art, Pottery
      - 17.29 Stockton at Forty: 1890
      - 17.30 Stockton Athletic Association
      - 17.31 Stockton Churches
      - 17.32 Stockton City Bank Building
      - 17.33 Stockton City Directory, 1870
      - 17.34 Stockton City Hall (1 of 2)
      - 17.35 Stockton City Hall (2 of 2)
      - 17.36 Stockton City Hall-Contract
      - 17.37 Stockton City Hall-History
      - (See Rolled Oversize Maps and Plans, Box 26) Stockton City Hall-Plans, 1923
      - 17.38 Stockton City Hall-Rehabilitation Project
      - 17.39 Stockton City Hall-Report
      - 17.40 Stockton City Hall-Research
      - (See Rolled Oversize Maps and Plans, Box 26) Stockton City Hall-Roof Replacement Plans, 2004
      - 17.41 Stockton City Seal
      - (See VHS Cassettes, Box 23) Stockton City Seal, 1997
      - 17.42 Stockton Civic Center
      - 17.43 Stockton Civic Center-Masters Thesis
      - (See Oversize, Box 25) Stockton Civic Memorial Auditorium-Construction
  - Box 18
    - Subseries: Stockton, 1850-2006 (cont.)
      - 18.1 Stockton Civic Memorial Auditorium
      - 18.2 Stockton Civic Memorial Auditorium-Inscription Debate
      - (See VHS Cassettes, Box 23) Stockton Concealed Weapon Issue, 1994
      - (See VHS Cassettes, Box 23) Stockton Development Center, Story of, 1997
      - 18.3 Stockton Diverting Canal
      - (See VHS Cassettes, Box 23) Stockton Downtown Development, [1995]
      - (See VHS Cassettes, Box 23) Stockton Downtown Promotion, 1996
      - 18.4 Stockton Early History
      - 18.5 Stockton Fire Department History Project
      - 18.6 Stockton Fire Department Research (1 of 2)
      - 18.7 Stockton Fire Department Research (2 of 2)
      - 18.8 Stockton Fire Department Station 13 Dedication
      - 18.9 Stockton Fire Department Training Tower Dedication
      - 18.10 Stockton Firefighters Memorial
      - 18.11 Stockton Golf and Country Club
      - 18.12 Stockton House / St. Charles Hotel
      - 18.13 Stockton Iron Works
      - 18.14 Stockton Library
      - 18.15 Stockton Mercado Project
      - 18.16 Stockton Neighborhoods Findings Proposal
      - 18.17 Stockton Ordinances